<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spears.network</title><link>//localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on spears.network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>links</title><link>//localhost:1313/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/links/</guid><description> Email LinkedIn Facebook YouTube Throwback Site TeamViewerQS</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>//localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid><description>After the realization that I would not be joining the military, I knew God had another plan in store for me. I had spent years building computers for family/friends, taking computer hardware/software classes in high school, and being the go-to tech guru. I knew the next step was to continue my education in Information Technology. I am a motivated self-starter with experience in Customer Relations and Computer Systems, and I have the proven ability to work well in difficult situations while providing a high level of customer service to clients.</description></item><item><title>Automated Profile Backup Using Windows Batch Scripting</title><link>//localhost:1313/posts/automated-profile-backup-using-windows-batch-scripting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/posts/automated-profile-backup-using-windows-batch-scripting/</guid><description>Introduction In this article I am going to go over the process of creating a script on backing up a user profile in Windows. We will be backing up the users Desktop, Documents, Downloads, Favorites (located in IE, Chrome, and Firefox), Music, Pictures, Videos, and even a list of the software installed on the machine running the script to refer back to when setting up the new machine. Utilities being used: echo off, color, cls, wmic, dir, robocopy, xcopy, and local variables (%backupdrive%, %profile%, etc.</description></item><item><title>Free Open Source Desktop Capture Tool - OBS Studio (How-To)</title><link>//localhost:1313/posts/free-open-source-desktop-capture-tool---obs-studio-how-to/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/posts/free-open-source-desktop-capture-tool---obs-studio-how-to/</guid><description>OBS Studio is free and open source, meaning there are no watermarks, no trial periods and it&amp;rsquo;ll never ask you for money! It is pretty much the only capture utility you will ever need. https://obsproject.com/</description></item><item><title>Search Engines with Privacy!</title><link>//localhost:1313/posts/search-engines-with-privacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/posts/search-engines-with-privacy/</guid><description>Discovering what someone is searching for on the web can show a lot of information about them&amp;hellip; Whether it be about their medical issues, financial situation, personal issues, or anything that comes to their mind. It will be searched, and in most cases it will be documented by someone. There are company&amp;rsquo;s out there that are making insane amounts of revenue from data packages that were collected on people. For example: Google has stated that they track things that you type into the search bar even if you don&amp;rsquo;t press &amp;ldquo;Enter.</description></item><item><title>Free and open-source software that you should be using!</title><link>//localhost:1313/posts/free-and-open-source-software-you-should-be-using/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/posts/free-and-open-source-software-you-should-be-using/</guid><description>Free and open-source software can offer the best solutions for desktop applications we need. They should be promoted more often than they are. However, big companies dominate much of this space by default by either installing software on your computer or using certain methods of directing you to their paid service. Unfortunately many companies are going to paid monthly models that trap you into spending lots over time, and going to free or open-source software can offer better solutions anyway.</description></item><item><title/><link>//localhost:1313/public/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/public/404/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> /404.html :~# 404.html/ about/ posts/ publications/ photos/ Page not found Return to the home page.
Powered by Hugo with Console Theme Dark.</description></item><item><title/><link>//localhost:1313/public/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/public/about/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> /about/ :~# about/ about/ posts/ publications/ photos/ About A minimal, responsive and light theme for Hugo inspired by Linux console. Modified from hugo-theme-console to add support for dark mode and sticky footer.
Installation $ mkdir themes $ cd themes $ git submodule add https://github.com/zx1239856/hugo-theme-console-dark hugo-theme-console-dark See the Hugo documentation for more information.
Configuration Set theme parameter in your config file:
theme = &amp;#34;hugo-theme-console-dark&amp;#34; License Copyright © 2021 zx1239856</description></item><item><title/><link>//localhost:1313/public/categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/public/categories/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> /categories/ :~# categories/ about/ posts/ publications/ photos/ Categories Powered by Hugo with Console Theme Dark.</description></item><item><title/><link>//localhost:1313/public/posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/public/posts/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> /posts/ :~# posts/ about/ posts/ publications/ photos/ Posts Aug. 3, 2019 Introduction Hugo is an open-source project and lives by the work of its contributors. There are plenty of open issues, and we need your help to make Hugo even more awesome. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a Go guru to contribute to the project&amp;rsquo;s development.
Jul. 1, 2019 What is Hugo Hugo is a fast and modern static site generator written in Go, and designed to make website creation fun again.</description></item><item><title/><link>//localhost:1313/public/tags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/public/tags/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> /tags/ :~# tags/ about/ posts/ publications/ photos/ Tags Powered by Hugo with Console Theme Dark.</description></item></channel></rss>